<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SuperHero-Room</string>

    <string name="superman_description">

        Kal-El was born on the doomed planet Krypton to Jor-El and Lara.
        Although Jor-El had hoped to send his pregnant wife away from the
        planet in a test rocket and avoid its destruction, Kal-El was born
        earlier than expected, and the life support systems could only support one.
        Therefore, the baby was sent alone to Earth, the last son of Krypton.

        The baby\'s spaceship landed in Sutton Field near Smallville,
        Kansas, where he was found by Jonathan and Martha Kent,
        who raised him as their son, Clark Kent. As he grew older,
        he began exhibiting extraordinary powers, including super-strength and flight.


    </string>

    <string name="batman_description">
        When leaving from a movie theater and back to home, Thomas and Martha Wayne
        are accompanied by their 8-year-old son, Bruce. However, unknown to them they
        would see their only son for one short last moment. Stepping into Park row
        (now called Crime Alley) out of the shadows is a masked gunman who killed both,
        Thomas and Martha. While their 8-year-old son watched their brutal death take place,
        Bruce\'s life would never be the same. At that moment, Bruce made a solemn oath to be
        an avenger of the knight and fight crime. That moment, Bruce Wayne died and Batman
        was born! Batman is the World\'s Greatest Detective and can handle any problem.
        He\'s one of the greatest heroes the world will ever know. Batman!
    </string>

    <string name="wonderWoman_description">

        Diana was the daughter of Queen Hippolyta, the first child born on Paradise Island
        in the three thousand year history that the immortal Amazons lived there.
        The Amazons had been created around 1200 B.C. when the Greek goddesses drew forth
        the souls of all women who had been murdered by men. One soul was left behind,
        the one that would be born as Diana. That soul originally belonged to the unborn
        daughter of the first woman murdered by a man (whom Hippolyta was the reincarnation of).
        In the late 20th Century, Hippolyta was instructed to mold some clay from the shores of
        Paradise Island into the form of a baby girl. Six members of the Greek Pantheon then bonded
        the soul to the clay, giving it life. Each of the six also granted Diana a gift: Demeter,
        great strength; Athena, wisdom and courage; Artemis, a hunter\'s heart and a communion with
        animals; Aprhodite, beauty and a loving heart; Hesita, sisterhood with fire; Hermes, speed
        and the power of flight. Diana grew up surrounded by a legion of sisters and mothers.
        When she was a young woman, the gods decreed that the Amazons must send an emissary into Man\'s World.
        Queen Hippolyta ordered a contest to be held, but forbade Diana from participating.
        Diana disobeyed and did so anyway in disguise, easily winning the contest and being
        named the Amazon\'s champion. She was given a uniform fashioned from the standard of
        someone who had visited the island a few decades earlier.

    </string>
    <string name="flash_description">

        Barry Allen is The Flash, the fastest man alive. Using his super-speed powers,
        he taps into the Speed Force and becomes a costumed crime-fighter. His position is a
        legacy in the Flash Family, successor to the original Jay Garrick and predecessor to Wally West.
        He is a founding member of the Justice League of America.Barry Allen and a twin brother were
        born on March 19, two weeks late, to Henry and Nora Allen in the small midwestern town of Fallville,
        Iowa. The brother was pronounced stillborn by Dr. Gilmore. However, in actuality,
        he had been born healthy, but given to another family, the Thawnes, whose child had died during birth.
        The lateness of Barry\'s birth only foreshadowed his bad habit of always being late.
        Barry grew up reading the adventures of his favorite superhero, Jay Garrick,
        the original Flash, and acted many of his hero\'s adventures out with his friend and
        future actress, Daphne Dean.When he was a child, his mother was killed and his father was
        convicted of the crime. The drive to prove his father was innocent gave Barry a strong belief
        in justice.
    </string>
</resources>